# WILLIAM CONNATSER

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

EMAIL: me@williamconnatser.com
PORTFOLIO: williamconnatser.com
GITHUB: github.com/WilliamConnatser
LINKEDIN: linkedin.com/in/WilliamConnatser

#### **SKILLS**

# Languages

HTML | CSS | Sass | LESS JavaScript | Node.js | Python

Front-end Frameworks

React | Vue | Blaze

**Back-end Frameworks** 

Express | Apollo GraphQL | Django | Flask

**Databases** 

SQL (Postgres & SQLite) | NoSQL

**Operations Management** 

Linux | Git | Docker

**Computer Science** 

Data Structures | Algorithms | OOP

#### **PROJECTS**

Maze MUD Escape <u>tinyurl.com/yy8o447l</u>

One week group project

React | Python | Django | PostgreSQL

- Multiplayer maze escape game made with HTML5 Canvas and WebSockets
- Largely responsible for the Django back-end and WebSocket implementation <u>github.com/cs19-maze-mud</u>

#### ChallengeJS

ChallengeJS.com

One month group project

React | Express | PostgreSQL | Auth0

- JavaScript coding challenge application
- Worked on all aspects of the stack
- Leveraged web workers to run arbitrary code client-side and run tests <a href="mailto:github.com/labs13-clone">github.com/labs13-clone</a>

#### Stockly

GetStockly.com

One week group project

React | Express | PostgreSQL

- Leverages sentiment analysis to predict stock prices and view market data
- Solely responsible for the entire back-end
- Architected data caching to get around API limit restrictions

github.com/lambda-stockly

# Bitcoin Maximalism Bitcoin Maximalism.com

Two month solo project

Vue | GraphQL | MongoDB | BTCPay

- Bitcoin-integrated social network
- User up-vote weighting is dependent on the amount of Bitcoin donated <u>github.com/WilliamConnatser/bitcoin-maxi</u> malism

#### **SUMMARY**

Hard-working Software Engineer who has been fascinated with computers since a teenager. Channeling that natural interest and curiosity into a profession fuels my daily growth and ambition. I obtain a strong attention to detail and the ability to work independently with little supervision.

### **EDUCATION**

### 02/2019 to Present

Lambda School

Full Stack Web Development

 Procured extensive experience programming full-stack web applications, CS fundamentals, and team workflows

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# 1/2018 to Present 6/2008 to 12/2014

**WEC Land Services** 

Software Engineer / Title Examiner

- Devised a web application for organizing a large ranch's numerous legal documents
- Integrated a web application with an FTPaaS API for easy viewing, downloading, management, and backup of documents
- Performed meticulous oil & gas title research to determine surface, mineral and royalty ownership of property
- Produced reports based on my research in courthouses using Microsoft Excel and Word

# **10/2012 to Present YOLO International LLC** Owner / Operator

- Performed administrative and accounting duties for multiple entrepreneurial projects
- Oversought the manufacturing and assembly of physical Litecoin collectors items including the secure generation of cryptographic keypairs and their concealment under tamper-resistant holograms
- Engineered, setup, networked, monitored, and managed large cryptocurrency mining farms which used numerous GPUs and ASICs

## 3/2015 to 4/2016 Adecco / Computershare

Customer Service Representative / QA

- Provided quality customer service experiences while utilizing large amounts of empathy and patience
- Garnered experience with nuance surrounding financial and legal services including proxy voting, bankruptcy, class action lawsuits, and mass tort
- Promoted from a temp agency to a full time employee with quality assurance duties
- Performed meticulous quality assurance by analyzing both inbound and outbound calls against company standards